LOTTE ENTERTAINMENT PRESENTS
Hello?
Why?
Okay?
SCHOOL ZONE
Directed by KIM Khan
THE NEIGHBORS
I'm home?
MY DEAD DAUGHTER HAS BEEN
COMING HOME FOR A WEEK
A missing woman has been found
dead in Gyeonggi-do again.
Residents in the neighborhood
are engulfed in fear
as a mutilated corpse was
found just last year.
The 14-year-old girl WON Yeo-sun
was found dead today at 10 am
10 days after she went missing?
TEN DAYS AGO
That one.
You got good taste.
I'll give it to you
for $130.
Sir?
Can you endorse this check?
Sorry.
Thank you!
Come again!
What a rude bastard!
Geez!
I'll take this one and a coke.
- That's $10.
- Okay.
Go ahead.
Sorry.
AHN SANG-YOON
I'm off!
Don't listen to music
when you're driving!
Okay!
Pizza delivery.
One combination and
a coke.
$10 please.
I think something fell.
Thank you.
Please sign the coupon.
You've ordered 3 times
this month!
If you order once more.
you get the 4th pizza for free.
I guess you order them
on certain dates.
- Go.
- Sorry?
Oh.
Enjoy your pizza, sir.
What a nasty guy.
Please.
Let me go.
Yikes!
- Are you okay?
- I'm all wet!
I'm sorry.
You live in unit 201 right?
I'll give you more toppings
next time you order.
It's not unit 201.
No?
I live in unit 302.
Don't forget those
extra toppings!
They look so alike.
The check's okay, sir.
Really?
What a relief!
- Would you like to deposit that?
- Yes.
Yeah?
Hello.
This is the Women's Society.
Uh-huh?
We're having the monthly
meeting tomorrow.
Please attend this time.
We need to get your sign
for redevelopment?
I'm moving.
What an asshole.
What are you doing
here, mom?
What are you doing here?
We had a lunch event
at the welfare center today.
I got one for Mr. HWANG
and Mr. PYO.
Focus on your studies!
You'll be in high school soon!
That hurt!
Where's Mr. HWANG?
Dunno.
He's never here.
We should just get him to quit.
Compose yourself, ma'am!
Can't do this anymore.
It's so frustrating.
Sir.
Please let me go home.
I won't say anything
if you let me go home.
I swear I won't say anything.
Go home then.
Who says you can't?
- Let's go home!
- Please! Don't hurt me!
Please!
- Help me!
- You're going home!
The police suspects that the victim
died of blows to the head.
What's wrong?
I think that's the suitcase
that I sold some time ago.
Don't you say things like that!
I'm sure it's the one.
Even if it is.
don't say anything.
We'd lose all our customers and
the police won't leave you alone.
Keep your mouth shut, okay?
Fine.
You're right. I'm not the only one
who sells that suitcase, right?
Murders in Sunae-dong, Jeongja-dong
and now Gangsan-dong?
That's our neighborhood!
Murder took place
in 10-day intervals.
Ten days?
2nd, 12th, 22nd?
That's every 10 days.
What are you muttering about?
Nothing.
This jerk orders pizza
every 10 days.
Enough nonsense.
You got delivery.
Okay.
We should thank him for
ordering at all.
I have to go back to work.
Get me some extra clothes.
I don't want to be here
alone anymore.
I'm behind work because
of Yeo-sun's funeral.
She came today!
Yeo-sun came home again.
- That's enough!
- I saw her.
So what were you gonna do
with that cross?
I'm so scared, honey.
You were gonna scare away
your dead daughter?
Only if I had kept my
promise that day?
Drop this already!
When will you stop?
Look!
You said she came home.
Where is she?
How can a mom be scared
of her own daughter?
I'd do anything to see her again
even if in my dream.
I guess you've never considered
her your own daughter.
Here.
Excuse me.
Yes, Yeo-sun?
Can I have some more soup?
Sure.
What do you mean "Excuse me"?
Call her ' mom'.
If that's hard.
call her 'step mom'.
Don't make her feel
uncomfortable.
That's okay.
We'll take it slow.
Long time no see.
What now?
- Come with us.
- Why!
Won't take long.
Thugs like him shouldn't live here!
We really gotta bulldoze this dump
- and kick out losers like him.
- Exactly!
This ghetto is attracting
too many of those people.
Look how nasty he looks.
Don't smudge it!
I'm dragged here every time something
happens just cuz I got one record?
One?
You mean seven.
Consider it lucky
you have an alibi.
I don't have time for this.
You nuts!
I'm off, okay?
Hey!
Stay out of trouble.
Now that we got your DNA on file.
you better be good.
DNA, my ass!
That little?
Mr. HWANG!
You saw the warning we got
about the food waste, right?
I can't take care of everything.
Maintenance is a lot of work.
You're never even in your post.
What do you mean, a lot of work?
Don't you know how scared everyone is
because of that dead girl in unit 201?
I heard her mother's
gone crazy.
Just do your job.
What mother wouldn't go crazy
after what happened.
Yes ma'am, I'll do
whatever you say.
Watch out!
- I'll guard the food waste
- Hey!
and maintain this place
like I'm mad
until my old bones crumble.
Are you drunk or something?
Geez!
I told you I'd kill you
if you don't pay back by morning.
You fucking with me or
something, Mr. KIM?
Please give me more time.
It's been six months.
Go and sell your organs
or something!
I'm your uncle, boy.
I'm your mother's brother!
Fuck you.
My uncle?
You're my uncle
when you need something.
Did I see you visit me
when I was in the hole?
When my mother died.
damn it!
Did you even show up
when she died?
So go to hell, uncle!
Hyuck-mo!
You use your own blood
for money, huh?
- You're dead this time.
- Hyuck-mo!
Hey!
Is that your car
on the handicap spot?
Yeah.
How dare you park your fucking car
in my spot?
What the fuck!
I'll move the car.
You!
Is that your spit on my car?
You?
You yourself, asshole!
There.
Now what?
I'll rip your fucking cheeks apart.
Scars, huh?
Are you in high school?
Move this fucking car!
Don't you get hot water?
Take a shower, you smelly asshole.
What a horrible smell!
Let's see who did this.
I got you good.
I'm getting a free drink today!
I know this is yours.
You can't trash food like this.
Stop annoying me!
Come one.
young man.
Just offer me a drink or something
and we call it even.
Do I have to show you
what's in here?
That's a tight knot!
Wait!
Fuck!
What the hell?
WON YEO-SUN
Is this the realtor?
This is Gangsan Complex
Block 11, Unit 102.
I can't rent the house right now.
I'm going to move later.
There are problems
with the house.
I'll call back when it's fixed.
Please leave a message after the tone.
Why isn't he picking up?
Did he go home?
Is HWANG not picking up?
Thank you for the ride.
No prob.
We're neighbors.
One second.
Can you hold onto this box?
I have to open the door.
Can you not look?
That's okay!
That's okay.
It's okay.
Be good.
Mom!
Feeling better?
I think so?
This is the best
when you can't digest.
That was so cool!
This is information about a donation
event from a welfare center.
Can I pass them out in the
neighborhood?
Donation event?
You can sign up too!
You live alone, right?
That's okay.
You can pass them
around, though.
Thank you.
I'll sign you up, too.
Okay.
Thanks.
It's late!
You should go home.
Good-bye.
- Get home safe.
- Okay.
Miss your daughter?
Pizza delivery.
Here's your coke.
That's $10.
Your house is so bright.
It hasn't been 10 days yet.
Enjoy your pizza.
You shouldn't have
been so nosey.
Did you go and check?
Nothing much there.
Just Junk.
Hello.
Hello!
It's you?again.
Gimme two of those.
These are very strong with
a hard shell and a lock pad.
I'll give you two for $200.
Let me dust them off.
Someone's calling me.
Hello?
Sang-yoon?
AHN Sang-yoon?
Nice to hear from you!
The lines must be confused!
Mister.
Yes?
Aren't you gonna count?
I think you gave me
the right amount.
You did, right?
Still haven't heard from him?
He's not picking up his phone.
Shoot.
He didn't quit cuz of what
I said yesterday, right?
I'm not sure.
Could you fill in for him
until he shows up?
Okay.
These units got a
high water bill.
Could you check for problems
in their water pipes?
Sure.
Thank you so much.
You never work during the daytime.
What are you gonna do?
What if someone recognizes you?
Just shut up!
NOVICE DRIVER
We fixed it a long time ago.
We called you several times.
I'm sorry.
Something happened.
This was in the car.
Excuse me?
Mom?
What is it?
Have you seen my head band
by any chance?
What head band?
The one that I wear every day.
It's metal with coils.
I haven't seen it.
It was my favorite one.
Mommy?
Mommy will buy you a new one.
Honey.
Yeo-sun doesn't know I bought a car.
I told her to wait so that
I can surprise her.
This weekend?
I'll ask Yeo-sun
if she can come with me.
Okay.
Hello?
This is the security guard.
- Hello?
- And?
Your water bill is high.
I'm wondering if you have a leakage.
Mister!
Are you home?
I'm from the Women's Society.
And?
I told you about the meeting
on the phone.
Let's talk inside.
Just do it here.
I don't want that unit
to hear this.
You know what happened
to their daughter, right?
It's unsafe around here
so we have to put a surveillance
camera in the front.
We also need you to sign
the redevelopment petition.
This meeting is very important.
I told you I'm moving.
What's with all your excuses.
young man?
I know you just moved in.
I rented this place for just
three months.
Look over there!
I see.
What's with all these
bright lights?
What the!
This house was so nice
before you came in.
How can this place be
ruined so fast?
It's like a haunted house!
Open the curtains, geez!
Hi!
I'm in unit 102.
I'll be up soon.
Oh my God!
I bought this
when I was travelling.
I'll give it to you as a present.
Hold on.
My daughter will like it.
Unit 102 is moving away.
We lost one vote.
No, no.
I'll be right there.
Take care.
Call if you need anything.
Bye.
Wait for me, I'll be there.
Who the hell parked like this?
You have room on the left!
Back up!
- Turn the handle to your left.
- What the?
Come on, back up.
Alright, alright!
Just a bit more, mister!
A bit more.
Okay!
Can I touch it?
Cool!
You know me?
You live in unit 202.
- What are you?
- I live on Block 10.
Here, read this.
It's about the block meeting.
- You a middle school student?
- Yes.
Read this then.
Call if you need help.
IMMEDIATE LOAN
I wonder whose they are.
Are you okay?
YOO SOO-YEON
You can lean on me.
I'm okay.
Be careful.
- Can we go in and talk?
- Sure.
You look so much like her.
We all do in school uniforms.
I'm sorry, anyway.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
Did you know my daughter well?
No. She was in a different class
and she was a new student.
She always seemed alone.
I've done nothing for her
as a mother.
My mom doesn't do
anything for me either.
Mom is a mom just by
being there.
Bye.
Yikes!
Oh, it's you!
You scared me!
I thought you were
Mr. HWANG.
This is for you.
You brought your snack
for me again?
Eat it when you're hungry.
Why are you here?
Where's Mr. HWANG?
It worked out that way.
I see.
I have to eat and go to
study academy.
Okay.
Be careful walking home at night.
My mom's coming to get me.
Bye!
You can't eat bread
cuz of your allergies!
Mr. PYO!
What's up?
Here.
Where did you get them?
I found them in front of Block 11.
- Block 11?
- Yes.
- Bye.
- Okay.
Aren't they Mr. HWANG's?
What?
I called before.
I have to check your pipes.
There's no leakage.
Then how come your
water bill is so high?
What's so suspicious about that?
It's not suspicious.
It's just strange.
- Won't take long.
- I'm moving soon.
If you're moving.
it really needs the inspection.
I'll be back with technicians
this evening.
Hold on!
You won't be long, right?
Everything seems okay.
You have a bathroom in the
basement, right?
I should check there, too.
Do you really have to?
Yes.
You can go first.
Finished.
- Where did you get these?
- In front of Block 11.
Block 11?
Are you okay?
What's wrong?
Just shut up.
What's that retard doing there?
The fucking asshole!
Come here, you fucker.
Come here, asshole!
I told you not to park
in my spot.
Did I not.
you piece of shit?
Fuck you.
What the fuck you gonna do, huh?
I'm sorry.
Sorry?
Don't park your fucking car
in my spot if you're sorry.
Get it out!
Keep your eyes down
or I'll kill you.
I'll kill all of you!
Sorry.
Were you studying?
No, Why?
Do you want to go
pick persimmons?
I love persimmons.
We should just leave them.
It's okay.
People pick them all the time.
I mean?we should leave some
for the magpies.
That's true.
Magpies have to eat, too.
Oh, I forgot.
I have to do the laundry.
See you.
I'm home.
Hi.
Go wash your hands.
Dad's coming home late.
Okay.
Umm?
What is it?
Nothing.
I'll go wash my hands.
Sorry, magpies.
MOM'S BIRTHDAY
STEP MOM'S BIRTHDAY
URGENT: CREW WANTED
DAEDONG leaves in two days.
But it pays less than SAECHANG.
Is that okay?
Doesn't matter.
Put me down.
Alright.
Since you're not a rookie.
I'll change your schedule.
Stamp.
You leave in two days.
- Your number's the same?
- Yeah.
What the hell is the
pin number!
Fuck!
The fucking bitch!
Let's just kill and leave.
I have to open the suitcase.
The pin number is set
to 000 by default.
I didn't touch it
so it should be 000.
Where are you?
Don't you have a key
for the suitcase?
No. There's only a number pad
for a lock.
Huh.
- Let me use your phone.
- Sorry?
My batteries ran out.
Do you like pizza?
Yes, I like pizza.
What the hell's wrong
with that bastard?
Hello?
Someone called you
from my phone.
Who?
- I'm not sure.
- What?
Someone from my shop?
What the fuck?
Hello?
What a jerk!
What's wrong with people today?
Fucking assholes.
I'm home.
Hi, hon.
You must be hungry.
Let's eat.
I'm so sorry.
Mommy didn't go out to get you.
You must've been so scared.
I'm so sorry.
Mom?
- Sorry I'm late.
- That's okay.
Mister!
Who is it?
You know my name.
AHN Sang-yoon!
Pizza delivery.
Pizza, sir.
What the hell's this?
What are you doing
in the middle of the night?
That man ordered pizza
and gave me this bill.
It has blood on it.
He could've hurt his hand.
Maybe, but it's so strange.
But you shouldn't loiter
like that at night.
Shouldn't we report him?
What did you say?
Do you wanna be arrested for
false accusation?
- False accusation?
- Don't stir trouble.
Residents here are scared
enough already.
It's late.
Go!
Okay?
Why did you do that?
You know he killed HWANG.
Shut up.
I see you wanna stay low
cuz you only have 5 months left
After hiding for 15 years?
and now call the cops?
No way.
I said shut up!
What a strange country.
You can kill someone and be innocent
if you hide for 15 years.
Shut up!
Just shut up!
Stop following me.
Get this straight.
You've been dragging me.
Shackled up in guilt.
You stole my thesis
and then took my life.
For 15 years you have never
apologized to me or my family.
What will you do now?
Yeah?
Move your fucking car!
What the fuck?
Which fucking car is it?
The fucking asshole.
You!
Move your fucking car.
You fucking crazy?
You pickin' a fight with me?
Fight?
Perhaps.
You wanna die.
you piece of shit?
You trying to make me
laugh here?
Kill me then.
Have you ever killed a man?
You're all talk.
Me?
I just kill if I want to.
Come here, you
motherfucking asshole.
You little piece of shit!
Let go, asshole!
I'll beat some sense into you.
Come here, you.
Say that again.
I'll kick your ass tonight.
I never liked you
from the start.
Wait.
Wait!
- What the fuck?
- I apologize.
You retarded?
I'll never bother you again.
Please stop.
What a pathetic bastard!
You mess with me again.
you're gone without a trace.
Stop fucking around and
stay out of my way.
God damn it.
Fucking asshole!
Spitting like a dog.
If you don't wanna end up like this
tell me the pin number.
I need my cell phone.
We're almost done.
Is this washed?
I said yes many times.
- It's being tossed on the floor.
- Really? I wonder why.
Whatever.
I'll just wear it.
- I'm off, mom.
- Okay.
Call me and I'II go out
to get you.
- See you later!
- Be careful!
Don't be so clumsy!
Hello, Mr. PYO!
Wait!
Do you walk home alone at night?
Of course not.
My mom picks me up.
Never walk home alone at night.
Take care of yourself.
Okay.
Bye.
Yes?
Police Station?
You're really leaving?
But he might do something
to Soo-yeon.
He's been following her
these days.
Her mom picks her up
every day.
What if she can't come?
Mrs. YOO reported HWANG missing.
The police are gonna storm in soon.
I just have 5 months left.
There is one way?
Keeping him away from Soo-yeon
without getting the cops involved.
She's like your daughter.
You can't leave her in danger.
Make him stay away from her.
Forever.
You know what I'm saying.
You've done it once already.
He's different from me.
The freak kills for fun.
We finished our inspection.
You can take it back now.
- Hello?
- This is unit 102.
How've you been?
You know the suspect has
been arrested just now?
The cops just got that bully
who lives in our block.
I guess it really was him!
This doesn't matter cuz
I'm moving soon
but what if rumors got out that
a murderer lived on our block?
It would be bad!
The real estate value will plunge!
Let's have the meeting a day earlier
so that I can come.
I'll also sign the petition then.
That's a good idea.
What time do kids come home?
Around 10 pm.
Why do you ask?
Let's do it then.
We should warn the kids too.
The prime suspect involved in the
serial murder in Gyeonggi-do
was arrested this afternoon.
According to the police investigation,
the prime suspect is Mr. AHN,
a man who lived in the same building
as WON, the last victim.
The police will start the
investigation with AHN.
AHN?
Who the fuck is this guy
KIM Sang-young?
KIM called you on his cell.
Don't gimme shit!
I don't know him.
He probably dialed the wrong number!
That's not my problem.
I'm back.
Who's that?
She's crying.
The wife of the bag shop owner.
The owner's gone missing.
- Owner of the bag shop?
- Yeah.
Sir, he's here.
Sit here, please.
Let's be quick.
You know this man?
He says you were with him
at 10 last night. Is that right?
Yes?
We had tea and left work
at around 10 pm.
Please record your message
after the tone.
Low batteries.
Yeah?
A suitcase with severed torso was
found near Gangsan Complex.
It'll take some time
for forensic results.
And?
They found a shovel
and cell phone in it.
The cell phone belongs to the
missing security guard.
According to call history.
a call was made to AHN Hyuck-mo.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, sir.
Where are the evidence?
Why did you say
we were together?
I would've been jailed
if you didn't.
Then you wouldn't have to
pay back.
I'll get the money.
Don't worry.
You're all talk.
Why are you pretending
to be on my side?
I'm your uncle.
Your mother's brother.
Enough with the uncle shit.
I know you lent me money
on purpose.
So that you can track me down.
Hyuck-mo?
When your mother passed away.
I was on the run for bankruptcy.
I couldn't go to her funeral.
Damn it!
Is it raining out?
You've been inside all day?
It's pouring all of a sudden.
You know what this is?
Where's KIM Sang-young?
I don't know who
KIM Sang-young is.
Wait!
This is?
Shit, it was unit 102.
Fucking asshole!
Shut it!
This belongs to someone else!
We'll see when we get
the fingerprint results.
Fucking asshole!
Low Batteries.
Help me!
Help?
Help who?
Building 11
Unit 102.
Help!
What are you doing here?
Are you going home?
You're getting wet!
This is great!
I couldn't call my mom
cuz I lost my cell.
Thank you.
Why the hell's she here?
There's a dent in this umbrella.
It was Yeo-sun's favorite umbrella.
It would undo all our efforts.
- What's going on?
- Is it a blackout?
Gangsan Complex
Block 11, Unit 102.
I think someone's been kidnapped.
Let me out!
You didn't do it, right?
Reporters are going nuts.
Don't let them know AHN's involved.
Yes, sir.
You're dead, asshole.
I guess there's a black-out.
It's so dark.
I guess so.
What's wrong?
Listen carefully.
From now on, don't look back.
Stick close to me.
Ma'am?
Hold on very tight.
What a bad timing!
Let's just meet later.
- Soo-yeon!
- Mr. PYO?
Soo-yeon!
- Hello.
- Is Soo-yeon home?
- What's the matter?
What's the matter?
Call her.
Call her right now!
She left her cell phone at home?
What's wrong with Soo-yeon?
Is something wrong?
What happened to my daughter!
Soo-yeon!
Are you okay?
Are you crazy?
You wanna get killed?
Get off the road!
Move!
Please find my daughter!
Please!
You asshole!
Damn it!
You piece of shit!
Fuck!
Mr. PYO!
This is because of that bitch.
I have your free pizza.
You got all the stamps?
Come in.
Can you check the pizza?
Get down!
You all barge in here like a
flock of fucking dogs.
You're dead!
You're all dead!
You!
You piece of shit!
What are you doing here?
You fucking asshole.
Where the fuck is your car today?
I'll kill you.
Is that a knife?
So you really do kill people!
You asshole!
Trying to fuck me over?
Hey!
Sir!
- He's stabbed.
- Sir!
Get the fuck up.
you crazy asshole.
We need an ambulance at
Gangsan Complex Block 11, Unit 102.
Hurry!
Piece of shit.
This psycho was my neighbor?
Where is Soo-yeon?
I don't know if I really killed her.
Or if she's still alive.
I'm confused too.
You're bleeding a lot, man.
That asshole's fucking crazy.
Mister!
There is one way.
You know what it is.
You've done it once already.
I'll be okay, right?
You'll be okay.
Ambulance's here.
- Will I live?
- I'm sure you'll live a long time.
Nothing to watch here!
Get back in!
Just calm down.
Hey!
You!
- Where's my daughter?
- Who are you?
- You're with that man from unit 102, right?
- Just let go.
Bring me my daughter!
Bring her!
Where's my daughter?
Come on, lady.
Damn it!
Please bring my daughter.
Mom!
There's your daughter!
- Soo-yeon! Soo-yeon!
- Geez.
Soo-yeon!
- Soo-yeon!
- Mom!
- Thank God.
- What's going on?
Thank you God.
Go ahead.
Get out of the way.
There's AHN!
AHN, you little!
Don't mind me.
Go check out unit 102.
Take him back.
- Come with us.
- Let go!
The killer's in there, dead.
Let me go.
We have evidence you're the killer.
That asshole set me up!
Let me go.
I'm innocent.
Fuck!
ONE MONTH LATER
Are you sure we don't
have to move?
I miss our daughter.
How much?
$180.
No checks, though.
I'll pay cash.
What's your name?
- Sorry?
- Your name.
Why do you ask?
I just wanna know.
Sang-young!
So strange.
What?
- I can't figure it out.
- What?
Why he didn't kill me right away
and kept me alive.
Don't start on that again.
When he came home, he would stay
near me and even sleep next to me.
Like he was terrified?
THE GIRL I KILLED HAS BEEN
GOING HOME FOR A WEEK.